As prophet TB Joshua prays for the people in Jesus' name,
the evil spirits lurking in their lives are exposed and they manifest, confessing their destructive activities.
He is finished!
What have you done to his career?
He is finished, he cant do anything again.
He only likes old women, because that's what I want him to do.
What have you done to his career?
He has no career anymore.
With one touch from the hand of God and he is set free.
Thank you Jesus for delivering me!
I'm free!
TESTIMONY TIME
Good morning, Church!
My name is Emmanuel Chigozie Madubuike.
I'm from Anambra State, Nigeria.
The woman next to me is my lovely mum.
So, in 2013 I got the opportunity to travel to South Africa.
Before I travelled, one of my friends told me that he needed to take me somewhere
so that I could fortify myself spiritually to be strong.
This was for me to be wealthier than anyone in my family or my friends.
I liked the suggestion because I needed money.
I followed that person to a native doctor.
On the way, my friend told me that the person was a very strong native doctor and that he knew him.
I asked him if he had been going there.
He told me not to worry for he knew him.
We went there.
The man asked me my name and I told him and gave him my picture.
He told me that before anything, I should deposit 50,000 naira and I told him no problem.
I withdrew and gave him the money.
I told him that he should convince me that he knew what he was doing as a spiritualist.
I lost my father in 2011 and he told me that he was in Abuja having fun with some women.
I was wondering which father he was talking about and looked at my friend.
He tried to convince me by telling me that I am a great man
but I needed to hear something more vital and specific about me than that to convince me.
He did an incantation and after all, he still said the same thing concerning me
and he told me that as he was talking to me, my dad was in Abuja with a woman in a hotel.
I was wondering what hotel he was referring to when someone had passed away.
I didn’t want to tell him anything; I wanted to make a fool of him.
After that, I called my friend outside and told him that I was no longer interested
for this man told me that my dad was having fun when my dad had passed away many years ago.
I entered again and told the man that I wanted to talk to him.
I told him that I didn’t need him anymore and that I wanted my things – picture and money.
He said that I couldn’t take anything back.
I pointed to my money on his plate and he told me that I could not touch the money again.
I agreed but still asked him if I could take my picture and he gave it to me.
I thanked him and drove out.
I told that man that I was no longer interested and I would travel the way I was.
I knew I would make it.
The man suggested another man again and said that this very man was very strong.
If this man didn’t convince me, I should not give any money.
I made sure that I slept in the same room with that guy so that he would not call the native doctor
and be telling him about me.
At a point, I started thinking that they were trying to take my money.
I told him that we were going on the next day but both of us had to sleep in my house.
He accepted.
In the following morning, we went to a shrine.
Immediately we entered the place, the native doctor looked at me and called me by my name.
I was shocked.
He told me the reason why I was there.
I confirmed.
I told him that he was the man I was looking for.
He said to me that before everything, I had to pay 100,000.
I told him that 100,000 was not a problem and that I would provide.
I thought paying 100,000 to get millions was OK for me.
Then, we drove out to withdraw 100,000 and we came back to him.
There were some things they asked me to buy – goat, chicken – to fortify me.
I accepted it.
I went and bought the things with the money.
When we came back, I handed everything over to him.
Then, he asked me to kneel down in front of the shrine and I did.
He told me to say everything I needed in front of the oracle.
I knelt down and told the oracle that I needed fame, money and power.
I needed everything.
I wanted to be bigger than my friends.
He told me that it was done.
He said that he needed to give me one advice, as he knew that I was going to South Africa which I confirmed.
He said that it was very rough area where they shoot anyhow.
I needed to fortify myself against gun.
That was a good idea.
I asked if I had to bring more money.
He said that I should relax for now because it seemed that I was afraid to bring money.
I told him that I was not afraid but if he did a good job, bringing money was not a problem.
He started fortifying me.
He killed a chicken and we all ate it.
After we finished eating at the shrine, he put one chicken feather inside my boxer.
Then, he brought a little stone and a red cloth which he tore into two to wrap the stone.
After that, he brought water for me to swallow the stone.
Before giving it to me, he used to the stone for ritual.
I swallowed the stone and it entered my stomach.
I asked him, “What else?”
Immediately I swallowed it, instantly, I was not with myself;
it was as if another thing came upon me.
My body became heavy.
I told him that he was really doing something for me, he was really strong and that I liked him.
I told him that I felt strong.
He said that it was time to test what he had done for me by shooting me as he brought out his gun.
I told him that he could not shoot me.
He reminded me that I asked for power and he had fortified me and done everything.
So, he needed to test it.
When you take an exam, you need to show what you studied.
After doing everything for me, they had to test it.
I asked him what would happen if he didn’t do things well and the bullet entered me
and I would die without my family knowing where I was.
I told him that as a spiritual man, I believed the spirit didn’t show him things well.
I asked him to test it on another thing.
He agreed but at the end, he still had to test it on me.
He put the feather and stone in a chicken and he shot the chicken which I paid for the bullets.
He shot the chicken more than six times but the bullets did not enter.
He said that I had seen this, it had come to my turn.
I looked at him and asked why he wanted to pressurise me and whether he wanted to kill me.
He told me that he had fortified me and he needed to test it on me.
I told him if he had fortified himself, I would like to test it on him
but I would not allow him to test it on me as it was impossible.
He told me that since I was afraid, I had to call my mum before the test, in case I died.
He challenged me by telling me that I am a man.
I told him that if he had to test it on me, I didn’t want it anymore.
I said that since he had fortified me and I had paid, I would say thank you and I needed to go.
He gave me one chalk and one bangle I needed to put on.
He told me that when I travelled, every morning, I should do incantation
and use the chalk to draw anything or write me name
and speak out what I needed and it would come to pass.
I agreed and collected those stuffs.
I went back to my house.
My flight ticket would be for the following week.
I realised that I would not be able to carry those things he gave me in my flight.
I had to come back to him because it looked like drugs as it was white.
I asked myself, "How am I going to take it on-board?"
He said that he would pack it inside a soap bar and seal it back.
He did everything and gave it back to me.
I went to the airport and I was a little bit afraid if they noticed it
but after scanning me, they did not see anything.
I entered my flight. I travelled succesful.
In my mind, I thought I would bring millions of naira back to Nigeria.
As I had been fortified and I was already inside the plane, I was enjoying.
I started singing that I would come back to Nigeria in a bigger way.
I arrived in South Africa.
In the morning, I did that incantation because I didn’t want to waste time.
I needed money immediately.
Everything I told this man to do for me – I asked him to make me wealthy and strong -
this man took everything and gave me serious poverty.
I stayed in South Africa for more than two years but I couldn’t boast of anything.
The residence permit – I didn’t have papers.
That really tormented me and even gave me sexual urge.
I didn’t like young woman.
In South Africa, I used to go out with old people who are above 50 years - that's my favourite.
My friends knew me.
If there were young girls, my friends would tell me, "This is not your 'food'. Your 'food' is old people."
OK.
We know you have lots of experiences to share with us.
We want to take you back for a while; so people would know the reason why
only Jesus Christ is the way, the truth and the life, and there is no other way.
There is no hope from spiritualists or witch-doctors.
You said you went to the second witch-doctor and he gave you a stone with a red cloth to swallow.
Could you tell us exactly what happened to you instantly you swallowed the red cloth with a stone
and what you started to see in your dreams, that manifested in the physical world?
OK.
Immediately I knelt down, he gave me a red cloth that has a stone in it to swallow with water -
I felt something heavy entered me - it was as if more than 50 giants entered me.
Every night, I started seeing myself making love with old people in my dreams.
I started making love with old people in the dream before I travelled and did it in my real life.
In the dream, I used to see dogs, lions fighting me.
Sometimes, I would wound them or they would wound me.
Immediately I woke up, I would scream in the house.
Everybody would wake up and asked what was wrong with me but I didn't want to tell them.
So, instead of witch-doctors, native-doctors making you rich and more prosperous,
it was poverty and nightmares?
Yes, that was what they gave me but what I went there for was for him to make me rich.
He collected my money and gave me poverty.
OK, you said that in the dream you started seeing old women making love to you.
What happened to you in the physical world?
In the dream, I started seeing old women making love with me.
Immediately they finished making love with me,
I would find myself automatically wet when I woke up and I would be very weak
and that day would be a very bad day for me.
In the morning or afternoon I would be thinking of an old woman
because I didn’t do things with young women.
After that, I travelled with it.
Everything that happened to me in the dream while I was still in Nigeria, I started doing it in South Africa.
I started sleeping with old women of 50-60 years – that was my favourite in South Africa.
Everything I put my hand on there was not working.
After seeing that nothing was working for me in South Africa, I applied for a job.
They would do interview on phone and after the interview, they would be impressed
and ask me to come to see me physically.
Immediately I appeared physically, that job would not be given to me.
I would not get that job again.
This happened to me once, twice, thrice – I knew the cause.
I called my friend that introduced me to that native doctor.
I asked him to remind me the reason we went to the native doctor because I forgot it.
He said that we went there for me to be rich and he was expecting me to send him money.
I told him, “You are very stupid.
Do you know that right now, I am begging to eat, talkless of sending you money?
Starting from today, deceive me no more!”
When I was there, I couldn’t boast of anything.
It was my mum I would disturb to send me money.
Almost every month, the money I used to pay my house rent in South Africa was from my mum.
I was in South Africa frustrated and tired – I didn’t know what to do anymore.
I prepared my passport and travelled to Israel.
When I was in Israel, God blessed me – I stared working in a hotel as a receptionist.
I could see that my life was changing.
I sent my first salary to my mum.
She was very happy.
She said that after many years, she just received my money.
I said, “Mummy, don’t worry. The bigger one is coming”.
Then, I was not is South Africa anymore where I should sleep with an old woman before I could eat.
I didn’t tell her about it.
While I was there, my papers got expired.
When I tried to renew my papers, they said that my papers was fake.
I asked them how I could have entered Israel with fake papers and even got a job with it.
They told me that the papers was fake and they could not renew it.
They did not want to arrest me because of my lawyer who was a strong woman.
I knew what was happening to me.
Immediately they told me that, I remembered what I did in Nigeria.
I knew that was the same thing that was following me.
I decided to come back to Nigeria to clear myself from darkness and fix my papers.
I came back to Nigeria to renew my papers which they called fake.
There was no way I could travel back.
I tried everything to go back but there was no way.
I called the company I worked for and told them that everything was OK.
They sent me an invitation letter to come back but there was no way.
That was what I was going through before I discovered Emmanuel TV.
I was in my house, frustrated, tired and angry with my life; I didn’t know what to do.
I turned on my TV to watch an action movie but it was not clear.
I was changing channels before I saw Emmanuel TV.
I saw Prophet T.B. Joshua praying.
I was sitting down alone.
I started watching the prophet praying.
I was thinking in my heart, he would not ask me to pay 100,000 or 50,000.
Then, I decided to come and see.
If he would also ask for money, I would run away.
When I stepped my feet in the arena of liberty, I began seeing a lot of changes.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I began seeing a lot of changes.
When the choir was singing, I could feel goose-bumps.
I could feel the real presence of God.
Everything that happened to me all these while, I began to view it.
I believed everything I needed and where I would get my deliverance was here.
I was wondering how could the prophet locate me where there were millions of people here.
It seemed to be impossible.
I decided to pray.
I believe as I pray, my problem would be solved.
Another voice was telling me that I was wasting my time as I was also praying before.
The voice asked me how this one would make a difference.
I began to reason with the voice.
I went outside and the irritation and anger came upon me again.
I went outside and bought a bottle of water and came inside again.
I was tired to stay there.
Immediately the prophet came in, I rushed back to my seat.
Prophet T.B. Joshua was touching people.
Behold, he went straight to my line.
I was among the people he touched.
What a wonderful God!
That is not enough for Jesus Christ - put you hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
It is a clear proof that weeping may endure for a night but the joy comes in the morning.
Indeed, he has suffered a lot, been to several places in search of a solution
but when it was God's time to manifest His deliverance in his life, it happened just like that.
Tell us; the moment the man of God laid hand on you - how did you feel inside you that brought about your deliverance?
Immediately Prophet T.B. Joshua laid his hand on me,
that 50 giants that entered me in the shrine where they collected my money - everything jumped out of me.
I was so free and became light.
I felt something came out of me.
The time those giants jumped inside me, I could feel it.
When they jumped out, I could feel it again.
That is not enough for Jesus Christ; put your hands together beautifully for the miracle working God.
You heard it all.
Right in the shrine he was possessed by 50 giants, and he knew they entered his life.
He said, that here, in the arena of liberty, when the man of God laid hand upon him;
the moment the giants left him, he also knew about it.
Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ once again.
Can you tell us; since you have been delivered - what are the changes you have seen in your life?
Since I have been delivered, I have no more urge for old women.
When they chat with me, I will be seriously irritated.
They know something is wrong because they don’t know that I am a new creation.
I am very free.
I don’t want to go back to my old life.
Amen.
What word of advice do you have for all who are listening to you?
The word of advice I have for young people is that you cannot go faster than your shadow.
Wait upon the Lord.
I ran faster than my shadow; I ran to get everything immediately
but I entered where they were destroying me slowly.
I thought I would be rich.
To God be the glory.